var questions=[
    {
        num : 1,
        question : "",
        answer : "Canada",
        options : [
            "Vanuatu",
            "Fiji",
            "Argentina",
            "Canada",
        ]
    },
    {
    num : 2,
    question : "",
    answer : "Bolivia",
    options : [
        "Marshall Islands",
        "Tonga",
        "Bolivia",
        "Palau",
    ]
},
{
    num : 3,
    question : "",
    answer : "Paraguay",
    options : [
        "Hawaii",
        "Samoa",
        "Chile",
        "Paraguay",
    ]
},
{
    num : 4,
    question : "",
    answer : "Montserrat(UK)",
    options : [
        "Bermuda(UK)",
        "Anguilla(UK)",
        "Falkland Islands(UK)",
        "Montserrat(UK)",
    ]
},
{
    num : 5,
    question : "",
    answer : "Nicaragua",
    options : [
        "Nicaragua",
        "Costa Rica",
        "Uruguay",
        "Panama",
    ]
},
{
    num : 6,
    question : "",
    answer : "Dominica",
    options : [
        "Australia",
        "Tuvalu",
        "Nauru",
        "Dominica",
    ]
},
{
    num : 7,
    question : "",
    answer : "Barbados",
    options : [
        "Barbados",
        "Tokelau",
        "Suriname",
        "Jamaica",
    ]
},
{
    num : 8,
    question : "",
    answer : "Uruguay",
    options : [
        "Bolivia",
        "Haiti",
        "Uruguay",
        "Guatemala",
    ]
},
{
    num : 9,
    question : "",
    answer : "Ecuador",
    options : [
        "Pitcairn Islands",
        "Ecuador",
        "Colombia",
        "Venezuela",
    ]
},
{
    num : 10,
    question : "",
    answer : "Cuba",
    options : [
        "Cuba",
        "Croatia",
        "Lithuania",
        "Austria",
    ]
},
{
    num : 11,
    question : "",
    answer : "Honduras",
    options : [
        "Uruguay",
        "Honduras",
        "Andorra",
        "El Salvador",
    ]
},
{
    num : 12,
    question : "",
    answer : "Panama",
    options : [
        "Panama",
        "San Marino",
        "Grenada",
        "Åland",
    ]
},
{
    num : 13,
    question : "",
    answer : "Puerto Rico",
    options : [
        "Czech Republic",
        "Costa Rica",
        "North Macedonia",
        "Puerto Rico",
    ]
},
{
    num : 14,
    question : "",
    answer : "Guyana",
    options : [
        "Trinidad and Tobago",
        "Sweden",
        "Guyana",
        "Bermuda (UK)",
    ]
},
{
    num : 15,
    question : "",
    answer : "Greenland(Denmark)",
    options : [
        "São Tomé and Príncipe",
        "Malawi",
        "Central African Republic",
        "Greenland(Denmark)",
    ]
},
{
    num : 16,
    question : "",
    answer : "Grenada",
    options : [
        "Grenada",
        "Seychelles",
        "Djibouti",
        "Gabon",
    ]
},
{
    num : 17,
    question : "",
    answer : "Bahamas",
    options : [
        "Burkina Faso",
        "Ivory Coast",
        "Tunisia",
        "Bahamas",
    ]
},
{
    num : 18,
    question : "",
    answer : "Saint Lucia",
    options : [
        "Senegal",
        "Martinique (France)",
        "Saint Lucia",
        "Anguilla (UK)",
    ]
}
];